This is addiction, pornography.
It's true.
You watch pornography.
And it becomes part of your blood.
It's true.
My wife was complaining, she said that I must stop reading.
Who?
My wife. She said that I must stop reading the Bible through my cell phone.
Whereas you are not reading the Bible, it's pornography you are watching.
It's true, it's true!
She will be complaining the whole night.
You see people today, when they say they are reading, when it is a different thing.
It's true.
Where is your wife?
She is back in South Africa.
I will invite her, don't worry. It is not an issue.
This pornography has destroyed your marriage.
Thank you, it is true. There is no affection between me and my wife.
You see your wife as a cheat.
It's true.
You just see anything bad about her.
It's true, it's true, man of God.
It's true.
My names are Tshiuhombera Tshiridzi Oscar.
I'm coming from South Africa.
I am an environmental consultant by profession.
Before you begin to talk, let me give a handshake to my sister.
I want to thank you for honouring this invitation.
And, I mean, ordinarily this woman would not come here.
Because it's just a phone call, and immediately
she said, "No, man of God is calling me, I have to be there".
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
The person beside me is my lovely wife.
She arrived yesterday.
Look, for you to know that you just have to continue to pray for this ministry.
After that prophetic word last Sunday, I said,
"You are not going home until I see your wife.
Because the home is broken".
And I had to give a phone call to the wife
and arrange how the wife can come down from South Africa.
Because if I allow him to go, I have not done anything.
The woman must be here.
If not, all is in vain.
The reason that brought me to the Synagogue Church of All Nations
was problem in my business.
There was stagnation, career failure, limitation.
You know, many of us we are here for certain things.
You don't know your problem.
What you are asking for is not even your problem.
He came because of business failure.
But the Lord is now telling him, "Your problem is pornography".
There is a broken home.
That is your problem.
Once that is solved, the business will start to ...
When you have a sickness, you'll hear, "I'm sick, I'm sick".
You never bother with the cause of that sickness.
"I have failure in business, that is our problem".
But what is the cause of that failure?
"I have a headache, please pray for me".
But you don't mind the cause of that headache.
This is why this problem continued to repeat again.
If you have not touched the root, and you remove the sickness - you are deceiving yourself.
Are you with me?
Soon, the business failure will come back, because the root is there!
It's like a stream of water flowing through somewhere.
And you try to clean up that water, what of where the water is coming from?
This is the problem of all of us today.
We never mind the cause of our problem.
We fight against the problem, but we never mind the cause.
I was very shocked when the man of God said, 'You are addicted to pornography'.
He just went straight, exactly to the root cause of my problem.
This problem started some years back.
1996, 1995.
My father told me that I had to go and wash his car.
Immediately I got inside his car, I found two pornographic magazines.
I collected those books and hid them inside my bedroom.
When my father left, I was busy looking at the pornographic pictures of naked women.
I became addicted to it, each and every day I would make sure to look at those pornographic books.
From then, 1999-2000, I began to be exposed to video cassettes.
I would wait for my parents to leave home, then I would be left alone, watching those video cassettes.
The year 2000, I impregnated a lady.
That was because of a spirit of lust.
Fornication was too much.
I started chasing women.
From there, the parents of the lady sent her to my house.
I rejected her, I said I didn't know anything about it.
After 3 months, they changed the story; they said that I had raped the girl.
They went to the police station, and I was arrested for a week.
After they finished investigating the case, they released me.
By that time I was 16 to 17 years old.
After they finished investigating the case, they said that they had arrested somebody who was underage.
From there, from 2000 until 2005, I was afraid to meet with any girl.
But in 2005 I met my wife. I was doing my final year at the university.
This problem affected me so much, because there was no affection between me and my wife.
I kept on lusting after women.
This problem caused me to have two children outside of the marriage.
My wife is only aware of one.
Now, would you listen to that?
Can you see? Are you listening to that?
My sister, you know you came here today to solve the problem once and for all.
No matter what happened, this is a husband God has ordained for you.
Ok?
If you are looking for a polished man to marry, are you yourself polished?
Ask your neighbor, "You are looking for a polished man to marry.
Are you also polished?"
You will polish the woman, and the woman will polish you.
Ask your neighbour,
"If you are looking for a polished man, a polished woman to marry, are you polished?"
We need to polish you.
You are like a shoe that is dirty.
Because the urge was too much, man of God, I promised to marry another lady and engaged her.
I married my wife legally, but I have already put the ring on this other woman.
My wife is not aware that I am already engaged to another woman outside.
So you have given a ring to a woman?
Yes.
Ok.
I learnt that the sister is here.
Yes.
This is why I am telling you that the case is very complicated.
But God will give us a way
So, because God wants to restore the marriage...
The sister that has been given the ring is here already.
But God will solve the problem.
So because for the sister to come here it also means she has a heart for God.
My sister, you listened to that?
Don't be surprised to hear that.
Just to make sure everything is alright.
Ok?
Ok.
The same Spirit of God that propelled you to come here, is the same Spirit of God that propelled that sister
to be here.
Should I bring you a seat? Go and bring the seat
for my sister.
Not that she is sick, I just want her to sit down.
Ok?
I have given a ring to that lady, my wife is not aware.
I have promised her that once I am back from SCOAN or after India for a massive project
I would marry her.
Eh? When?
I used to beat my wife each and every day.
When I look at my wife, I don't know what would make me angry.
I would see my wife as a cheat.
In fact, I was already 95% outside the marriage already.
It is alright, it's alright. We don't want to hear, we are here for reconciliation.
We don't want to hear anything that will not glorify the reconciliation.
Ok, thank you.
My sister, please, to settle the marriage and everything, ok?
I will call the sister out, ok? I hope you don't mind.
Ok, thank you.
Thank you.
The other lady is also not aware that the man is married.
But this is how you men, you guys
do deceive people out there.
So, may God forgive all of you people.
I can't hear an 'amen.'
Amen!
For my sister to be here, you don't need to be told -
if she was the kind of person that doesn't want to hear God, you would not see her here
because of the nature of the matter.
For her to be here, I want to thank you very much.
Thank you for coming here.
And I want to assure you that your situation is my situation.
Your problem is my problem.
I will make sure you come here with a great testimony.
Thank you for honouring the prophet.
If you honour a prophet because he is a prophet, you receive a prophet's reward.
Thank you.
I am convinced that she is sorry
for what happened.
I have not heard from her, I am just seeing her for the first time.
She is very very sorry, she never knew, she cannot be part to a broken home.
Ok.
So that is it.
So please, your ring, you will collect your ring and she will give you your ring.
Now my sister is not interested.
So sorry, and sorry, it's over.
So please, that is it.
I think I will end the message like that.
I want to see my sister. Can you take my sister, go and sit down somewhere there?
I will see her after service.
You came from South Africa?
Yes, I came from South Africa.
Thank you very much, I will take the responsibility. Ok?
So, go and wait for me.
Thank you.
When you have the fear of God, you will do every proper thing to reconcile,
to say sorry.
She has the fear of God.
If God had to share a reward among the three, she would receive the greatest reward.
Are you with me?
If God wanted to share a reward among the three people here -
that lady in red, that you see as the offender, she would receive the greater blessing and greater reward
for what she has done now.
So, that is God for you.
For somebody to actually come from South Africa over this issue...
And she knew what she was coming here for.
But the fear is, that ring, she said, "I must see prophet TB Joshua,
and hand over this ring to prophet TB Joshua, and say I am sorry for what this man has caused".
Just like that.
So, are you listening to me? Thank you very much.
I am happy you are laughing now.
The old has passed away, every other thing has become new.
Ok? Can you just say sorry to your wife, whatever you have caused your wife.
No, no, no, no, don't go down on your knees. Stand up.
Don't go on your knees.
I am very sorry, my wife. I am very sorry.
It's ok.
Thank you.
So, I want to meet them, I want to meet them.
And my sister there, too.
Ok, I understand what she demonstrated now.
The sister there.
So I quite understand her.
I will not allow her to talk, but I know what is in her mind.
And I say, madam, can you see?
If God could go all this way, or go too far to reconcile your marriage...
So please, give your best to this marriage.
You are a mother to him.
Ok?
You have to tolerate him.
And he himself also has to tolerate you.
You are because she is, and she is because you are.
So, please, where he is weak, you are strong.
Where he is strong, you are weak.
Please tolerate each other. Thank you very much.
So I will meet them, let them go and have their seats.
I am very sorry to my wife.
I want to..in fact, as from now, it's like the first day when we met some years back.
I love my wife so much. I love her so much, and I am so very sorry, very, very sorry to my wife.
After my deliverance, the day I saw my wife when she arrived here, I couldn't even help myself.
I ran to her, I hugged her, I kissed her in front of everyone.
I love my wife so much.
So much. I love you, my wife.
I love you.
I am very sorry, my wife, I am so sorry. Please forgive me.
I forgive you. Please.
I love you.
After my deliverance recently, that very same day I felt like there is something which went out of my middle finger,
middle finger, like somebody had put a ring on it; that ring came off.
In my dreams I am no longer seeing the spiritual wife, or ladies on the queue to sleep with me in my dreams.
I love my wife so much.
I am no longer interested in seeing naked women, I love my wife.
I am delivered. I am free from those spirits of pornography.
I thank God because the devil is out of my marriage,
the devil is out of my family,
the devil is out of my life,
the devil is out of my business.
Thank You, Jesus!
I want to thank God, because this thing was tormenting me so much. I was crying each and every day.
For I was praying each and every day that He would locate this problem.
But I thank God because He located it, and my problem is over.
My pain has passed away, I thank You, Lord.
And I thank God because He used prophet TB Joshua to deliver my husband.
Now he is a good husband and a lovely one.
I feel so great because my husband loves me so much
after the deliverance. When I came here on Saturday, I was surprised
because my husband came to me quickly and hugged me, and kissed me.
I was not expecting such a thing because he doesn't do this.
I thank You, Jesus, because You delivered my husband.
I feel like it's the beginning of this marriage; and I thank God because we are starting a new relationship.
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Thank You, Jesus. Thank You, Lord.
I have forgiven you, my husband.
Association brings assimilation. I have associated myself with pornography
and behaved like the characters in pornography films or the sex workers.
My advice is this, if you have made a mistake as we all do, don't run away from God; run to Him.
Thank You, Jesus.
The man of God, Senior Prophet T.B.Joshua, with Emmanuel TV partners all over the world,
have realized the need to also help you financially, also the Man of God said we should give you
a sum of $1,000 to assist you back home and also enable you and your wife to remain at peace.
We thank God. Thank You, Jesus. Thank You, Jesus for using the Man of God to bless my marriage.
Thank You, Jesus. I've never expected that the Man of God would bless me with such a huge amount.
Glory be to God. This is the only ministry which I know that when you come here - you can never
go back the same. I thank God. Apart from delivering me and restoring my marriage
man of God blessed me with a sum of $1,000. I've never expected this.
God bless this ministry and God bless the Man of God, Senior Prophet T.B Joshua.
Thank You, Jesus.
My name is Mahada Shunsani.
I'm from South Africa.
I am a senior accounting clerk; that is a cashier supervisor.
Last Sunday, the man of God invited me and I came here to the SCOAN.
That was after I saw the deliverance of the guy I was dating, called Oscar.
He was being delivered that Sunday which was the man of God's birthday.
When I was watching Emmanuel TV at home, I saw him being delivered.
Then the man of God said he was addicted to pornography and it had destroyed his marriage.
As I was one of the girls he was dating, I felt in my heart that I maybe was one of the major causes
or people who had broken their marriage.
We were dating. He proposed to me and gave me an engagement ring.
As the man of God was prophesying, I realised that what I was doing was wrong.
Within the week, I got an invitation from the man of God to come to The SCOAN.
I found out in my heart to say this was my chance as I knew I also needed to be delivered
and what I was doing was wrong. I could not stand to see me destroying someone's marriage
because if it happened to me, I would not like it.
When the man of God called me to come here, I found it worrying.
Even though it took me time to be with him, I knew it would cause my life to be unhappy.
I had to come here for my own deliverance, so I would get my own husband, family and home.
When I was watching Emmanuel TV that very Sunday when Brother Oscar was delivered,
Prophet T.B. Joshua spoke about love and offence, just like the message he preached last week.
Then, I felt it in my heart that I had offended his wife and abused her emotionally.
When the man of God was talking about love and offence, I said to myself that there was no way
I could say I was praying and expect God to hear when I was still offending her.
I then felt I should tell her that I love her from my heart and put myself in her shoes.
If I were in her shoes and this happened to me, what would I do? Would I be happy with that?
After the man of God spoke about offence and love, I decided to take this chance.
On that Sunday, I sent her a text message and asked her to forgive me.
I asked her to find a place in her heart to forgive me because I knew I had offended her.
When the man of God invited me, I couldn't wait. I wanted to fly the same moment I got the call.
I was so happy, knowing I was going to get my own portion of deliverance
and have a chance to say sorry to her in a way she would understand.
When the man of God called me out, I felt honoured
and introduced myself as the woman Oscar had engaged.
As the man of God talked to me and held my hand, I couldn't think of anything else.
I felt peace from there and knew that this is what I wanted - to be out of this relationship.
I had been struggling for long but this was my opportunity and time to be delivered.
I felt peace when he talked to us and told his wife that this was her husband from God.
When he told me God would provide my own man, I felt so peaceful, released and free.
When he called me to his office and I met him, he prayed for me
I just felt free. I felt that urge and desire to leave me.
When he prayed for me, I collapsed, vomitted and then afterwards felt free.
It felt like something came out of me; I felt so relieved and free.
I realised after he prayed for me that what I was doing was wrong.
I could not be in love with someone who is married and break someone's house.
I felt free after that and I know I am delivered for good.
Currently, I just want to say I am sorry to his wife.
I know I abused her emotionally because she knew of our relationship
but didn't know what to do about it because we kept going back to each other.
So, I want to say sorry to his wife and give back the ring to Oscar to say I don't need it anymore.
I know I will have my own portion, so I want to give the ring back and say sorry to his wife.
What I can say to the ladies out there is that God's delay is not God's denial.
Learn to be patient. I have realised I should have been patient and wait for my own husband.
So, be strong and wait for the Lord's time because God's time is the best.
God's delay is not God's denial.
The man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, in his usual kind gesture
knows fully well that we wouldn't want you to go just like that.
He also said he would like to bless you with the sum of $1.000 to assist you back home.
This is from Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world.
I thank you very much for this gift I just received from the man of God.
I am very grateful and thankful. Thank you very much. You have honoured me a lot.
May God richly bless you. I thank God and I thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The man of God has done this for me; I really don't know how to express myself.
I was not expecting this gift or anything except for me to confess and be prayed for.
Now, I have received deliverance, peace of heart, this gift of $1.000 and The Mirror book.
It's a lot to me and I am very thankful and grateful.
I just want to say I am sorry to them and give them their ring.
Reconciliation Testimony
Now, I want to say this to Oscar. I am bringing this ring in peace.
Now the man of God has delivered you and told you that your marriage is from God,
I believe it and I am bringing this ring in peace.
I would like to advise you to have your house in order and enjoy your marriage.
May you and your wife please find it in your hearts to forgive me
as I am bringing this ring back to you.
I forgive you and I am very sorry. I also ask you to forgive me.
It was not myself but the spirit of pornography which was pushing me.
I was being tormented by the spirit of lust and fornication.
I am very sorry for wasting your time.
After my deliverance, I realised that what I was doing was totally wrong.
I want to let you know that God loves you more than the way I love you
and I wish you the best.
May God bless you as you have your future partner, in Jesus' name.
Reconciliation Testimony
I just want to say to you that I am very sorry.
I know I abused you emotionally.
I know that what you were going through was not good.
I have realised that what I was doing was wrong.
Now that I am delivered, may you please forgive me.
May you please find it in your heart.
Reconciliation Testimony
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me. I'm very sorry.
Reconciliation Testimony
I have forgiven you. I love you so much, my sister.
I have forgiven you with all of my heart
and I love you so much, my sister.
I wish you the best.
Thank you.
Reconciliation Testimony
Thank you, Jesus.